Hello, Mr.
Wade.
Mr.
Wade was my father.
Just call me Wade.
All right.
My wife's last name is Lee, so I actually like going by Mr.
Lee sometimes.
Preferably with the accent, Mr.
Lee.
My last name is Brown, and my neighbor's last name is White.
And boy, is he tickled by that?
Like he came to deliver some mail.
He's like, I didn't know you were white and I'm brown, or you're brown and I'm white.
Okay, he's like a 75-year-old.
He's a super nice guy.
I predict Cassadas forgot.
He linked the message to me saying that this was happening.
Oh, that was me.
I did that.
Was it?
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to call him.
Well, Dave linked the copy of Cassada's.
Oh, yeah, I see it now.
Dave admitted whole quoted Cassador.
Forwarded to voicemail, not a good sign.
He turned his phone off.
Is he traveling or something?
No, he's back.
He has no excess.
I could try Natasha.
She'll be really annoyed if I call her.
Yeah, I don't think she likes us.
It's only 9 p.m.
My only experience with her is she likes Amy more than me.
Oh, there he is.
Here I was debating whether to call Natasha or not.
I don't have to do it.
So no, no, it's definitely.
We weren't sure if you're gonna make it.
I was gonna make it.
May not make it.
Come on, man.
Of course, I'm gonna make it.
If you remember, it's hard to remember sometimes.
I forget.
I mean, this is off schedule.
Yeah.
And it is pretty early for me, too.
Oh, Stéphane, you jumped.
Yes, I'm here.
And from Stéphane.
France.
Oh, it is 6 a.m.
Yeah.
I've done the 6 a.m.
game.
He's like, he's showing real commitment because he lives in France, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Oh, dear.
No pressure for us to give a good session then.
I'm in Manhattan, so this slot will be midnight.
Next week, I'm on an airplane.
Well, Tuesday, I'm on an airplane.
Well, we should find a way to.
Okay, let's see.
Back Friday night, though.
Let's play.
All right, let's play.
All right.
We're all here.
Let me actually load up my character sheets and such.
I provided appropriate summaries.
I missed a dragon attack.
What the hell?
Actually, what you missed was something far more spectacular.
It's me single-handedly defeating a dragon with spell.
I saw that.
I saw that the bard got bardic behavior for once.
Great.
And I negotiated an enemy if my enemy is my friend.
Yeah, that was very ally.
That was not.
Yeah, that was.
That hit different.
I need to get something to drink.
Hold on, hold on.
We force it.
Well, what he didn't write about was how you then lied about it to all of us, but I guess we're changing that.
Yeah, I was hoping she would just not realize that that was a problem.
By the way, I signed up a new ally, JK JK temporarily, our enemy.
Oh, we have our enemies.
It's just a ruse.
All right.
So hold on.
Let me just make sure I remember what happened.
Yeah, it's important that GM knows.
Stéphane, where do you live in France?
I live in a city called Clermont-Ferrand.
That's right smack in the middle of France.
In the middle of nowhere.
It's a rural area.
It's where the old volcanoes are.
Oh, no, very fertile plains.
And I mean, the only, I guess we're famous for a few things.
One is the rugby team.
We got a good rugby team.
Two, we've got a black cathedral because it's made out of volcanic stone.
Okay.
And three is that we've got the new headquarters.
Is it like between like Lyon?
Yeah, sort of.
Yeah.
Sort of.
Okay.
Between Orleans and Lyon would be sort of a diagonal, I guess, from north, somewhere in the up north to the east.
And Clermont-Ferrand would be south of Orleans and west of Lion.
Okay.
He's like Clermont-Ferrand.
Clermont-Ferrand.
Oh, I see it on the map now.
I see it.
It's not that small.
It's on the map.
Pretty cool looking cathedral.
Thank you.
Yeah.
All right.
Here we go.
So, question on roll 20.
Is there a way to see the character sheet in roll?
Oh, yeah.
So we use DD Beyond.
Okay.
And so I did not buy the entire DD set twice.
All right.
But there is a way to connect the two with a Chrome plugin called Beyond 20.
Okay.
Highly recommend.
Which will roll your character dice into the DD Beyond right.
That's why I was asking you.
Yes.
DD Beyond has created a looking for virtual tabletop, which I may at some point decide to switch to, but not today.
It has some like nifty properties in particular around generating encounters.
All right.
When are we switching to Discord?
Because Gary still works at Google.
We should wait until he's done.
Is that really the case?
That's what I was hurting.
Yeah.
All right.
What a Discord server or whatever.
We just make one.
All right.
Who's got that accent out of it?
Wade.
I'll create a Discord.
I will create a Discord server.
Oh, okay.
Vukradin's.
In fact, I have one.
It's called the Welcome to the Original DD Club.
The one that you use with all your other friends?
No, no, it's the one that you are on.
Erie, do you have a do folks have a Discord ID?
Wade, do you?
What's your Discord ID?
Waaaade.
How many A's?
Five.
Waaaade with five A's.
All right.
How do I add a member?
Drop the link into the Google chat.
Yeah, do that.
Do you right-click your server and say invite people, and that'll give you a link that you can session.
Yeah.
There.
I put it in the chat.
Yep, I got it.
Yeah.
I roll twice.
Log in.
All right.
Okay.
So you're all in the pub, right?
So let's see.
Rupert and shall we start with people asking me what happened to Lokudus?
Yes, yes.
Yes, that is definitely what you should.
That is definitely something we should start with from Vukradin.
Vukradin's gone to his store.
Aine has gone to her store.
Adabra has gone to and Jenerith is loosing her wounds.
Loosing her wounds.
All right.
Okay.
So do you want to tell them what happened this time, the truth?
Yeah, they're asking me what happened to Lokudus and I'll say, oh, yeah.
A sister, what's her name?
What's her name?
Kella.
The sister?
No, no.
She said that she would work with us to beat the Carver.
No.
We don't work with evil people.
What is this evil thing you're talking about?
He is.
Let me put this in terms you can understand.
Enemy of our...
Yeah, but he's enemy of our enemy.
She's in her enemy.
No.
She is our enemy.
She is our enemy, but she is also enemy of our enemy, which provides good negotiation options.
I will have nothing to do with this.
Wait, so that means that...
She told us how to find the Carver.
How do we find her and kill her?
Didn't you get to attack?
Did you let her go?
You had her in your grasp and you just let her walk away?
She offered a good negotiation deal.
Let me guess.
She offered you some treasure, too, didn't she?
Did she offer a stretcher?
Yeah, she offered you the reward that she was going to give to Lokudus.
She offered you as a down payment for your relationship.
Oh, we earned that, though.
Earned stolen.
How many times do I have to tell you people you can't earn stolen goods?
You can earn it.
You just can't keep it.
All right.
I need to go take a walk outside.
I need some air and a cigarette.
I'm leaving the tavern.
You're leaving the tavern.
I'll talk to the hand for a while.
The face has left the building.
Okay.
What happened to him?
He had a very strange reaction.
He's a man of principle.
Don't you know?
What does that mean?
Principles of self-defense, the survival of the fittest.
He doesn't think people should lose their possessions because they, you know, fell out of their pocket for some reason.
But if they could be useful.
He thinks they belong to their original owner.
If they're so alive.
I mean, you don't know that they're alive or not.
He doesn't know they're alive or not.
He needs to find out if they are.
Great.
We will go on this adventure to figure out who these owners are and if they are dead.
Yeah, that's the only problem.
I think if we find out they're dead, he still has issues with taking the money.
I do kind of have a draw a line there, but he doesn't.
Jenerith is looking at you, and then two of the villagers show up while you guys are having this debate and say, are you Lascleric?
Are you a believer in the purifying pain of the sun?
Yes, his brain.
We have been waiting for years for someone to see the truth that Lathander's glory is in feeling his pain while it sears you and brings you purity.
See the searing truth.
So they're like, so will you be establishing a chapel?
That's a good idea.
Actually, kind of is.
Will you be establishing a chapel?
Okay.
Where?
Oh, we got some money here.
Christ.
Don't tell Vukradin.
I'm not in the room.
Go right.
All right.
Well, okay.
We need to get some names.
Hold on.
Alexa, turn on the lights.
I know, Calasunis, your camera is off if you didn't know.
Oh, it is?
Sorry.
It doesn't bother me.
No, no.
Just make fun of me if I did it.
So, you know.
Yeah, I'm not sure what this arc is that will teach her Overbright ways, but we're going to have to figure this out.
Teacher, what?
Hold on.
So where are you going to put the chapel?
I don't know.
Where is there a space in town?
I look at the map on Roll20.
Surely one of these unlabeled buildings could just become the chapel, right?
Yeah, you could repurpose a building or you could build a new building.
Do we have enough gold to build a new one?
Enough free trade goals?
I don't know.
We could ask for a contribution from the faithful.
You probably would need me to do that.
Maybe I should work on renovating this Tresendar Manor.
So the first one introduces himself as he's fair-skinned.
Bundlewine.
Yes, Bryn Bundlewine.
Yeah, he introduces himself as he's got fair skin and haircut.
And you also see Iles Slipper-Shine with footed eyes and restless hands.
And they're both very kind of like excited to see you.
You also notice that they're very pale skinned and they've got a lot of sunburns.
Oh, okay.
Sort of the anti-Valphine.
Right.
And so they're kind of like, we've heard, we've heard that.
We've heard that you too believe in the pain and the purifying pain and the religious ecstasy that comes from worshiping pain.
Is skin cancer a thing in the DD universe?
Sure.
Most people don't live that long.
He's certainly Forgotten Realms, and I think he's also Kakasnis, or is there a translation?
There's a different god there.
But it's still a sun god, right?
Yeah.
So he goes, We have heard that you are one.
The first one goes, we have heard of you.
We heard rumors of a drow who worships Lathander, and we thought only Drow could understand this message that we believe in, that it is through pain.
Yes.
Your first orders will be to clean up this.
Tresendar Manor.
It is now our new temple.
What?
Tresendar Manor.
Oh, oh, Tresendar Manor.
You want us to go clean that?
That will be our manor.
Harbin, who happens to be around, shows up.
The Privy Council has voted that the Tresendar Manor will be the new chapel to the god Lathander.
Yeah, no, well, you're not there right now.
So Harbin says, did I hear that you're interested in turning the Tresendar Manor into a religious building?
That is correct.
Well, I think that's a fantastic idea.
Great.
You can help too.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But, you know, current in receivership, and, you know, a small fee would be required to clear up the paperwork.
What?
Possession is nine-tenths of the law, right?
The corruption in this town.
In this party.
He noticed you're not here, right?
I'm not here.
Yeah, I'm still appalled.
He's taking advantage of the fact that you're not here.
I'm sure he is.
He's like, look, I think the Privy Council and I could get to an arrangement where we could give it to you for a very small fee.
Do I feel like I need to purchase it or do I feel like I just appropriated it?
Well, she goes, you wouldn't want the Privy Council to accuse you of stealing it now, would you?
Keep in mind, I lead the Privy Council.
He's on the Privy Council.
Now, if you were to do this, this could be a private matter that the entire council doesn't need to be exposed to.
Is this the way things happen in the Overbright?
Sometimes.
He goes, you know, I think of it as.
He pauses.
Yes, the Overbright.
What is the gloriously bright sun?
Paint fills up.
He's like, Harbin goes, that's actually quite clever.
Is that I didn't know that.
Wouldn't you know?
Yes, this is how things are done in the Overbright.
And I'm looking to Wade to help me translate.
It's a deal we make.
You help me, I help you.
Yes, deals.
Yes.
You get deals.
You know, this is arrangements.
The town needs some money to, I don't know, do beautification of sorts.
And so I could very easily arrange for the paperwork to be passed the property on to you.
This is a good thing.
Oh, okay.
I mean, well, good in quotes.
Again, who probably won't approve, but he doesn't need to know.
He doesn't need to know.
Things are done here.
He goes, yes.
For better or for worse, yes.
Lathander be pleased.
Marie, what do you say as you observe this whole thing?
I'm still scratching my head.
I don't think I'm smart enough to understand what's going on, really.
And Toblen, by the way, is telling Toblen to keep bringing you beers.
Right.
I'm pretty happy.
Harbin's telling, it's kind of going like this to Toblen and like that to get you to get some beers.
Toblen, every time you're finished drinking, Toblen shows up.
Barbarian ways that it's an all-disc communal property.
Okay.
What was the fee?
Did we hear about 50 gold pieces?
And how much of Sister.
What's her name?
Gella.
What?
How much money do we get from Sister Gella?
Oh, for gold pieces.
Oh, so we have that lying, your honor.
That's convenient.
Did you put the add the difference to blood money?
Sure.
Blood money.
All right.
Okay.
And we'll have to make sure that we decorate the church order with lots of spikes and chains.
Just want a bunch of windows?
Yeah, well, I mean, we shouldn't cover over the roof.
Skylights.
You need actual skylights.
You'll notice on the map it now says Temple of Searing Pain of Justice.
Where do I?
You should see it, right?
I don't think I see.
Yes.
I see it.
Oh, I'm just blind.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's in red at the right far east.
Okay, I got it.
Yeah.
So you now have that.
It now belongs to you.
Right.
We're well on our way to play.
What?
You don't approve?
No, I'm kidding.
It's good.
Let me see if I can get that would work better.
Temple of Lathander's Searing Pain of Justice.
That's more legible.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Red one was not really legible.
All right.
Okie dokie.
So Ren and Giles are off to the temple to spruce it up.
Yeah, so they're going to be doing that for a few days.
Sprucing up is going to cost some money, Gary.
And they're not paying.
Or pay them before I get back.
Well, I mean, not for them.
They're doing it.
The labor is free, but they need to buy stuff, right?
Okay.
I mean, like, beams, you don't like construction material.
So they're going to say, you know, 25 gold pieces.
We'll get it set up correctly.
Latest is appropriate.
Seems a little high, but.
Should be able to haggle them down.
You will cut trees.
It's right next to a forest.
He goes, yes, yes, it is.
That's true.
Right.
But, you know, we have to buy.
We have to buy furniture.
I mean, yes, we'll do a lot of the hard work.
Your grace will do it.
Your grace, your grace.
But the point can be reverend mother.
The uh, what do they say in the drow communities?
That's uh the matron mother, matron mother, yeah, matron mother.
So, you're gonna go with the matron, matron mother of Lathander.
There we go, except when Lathander finally connects with you, you're high enough level for the to come up and you know, do you consider that this is part of global vision here?
It's not.
Have you considered the possibility that you know he's testing his religious followers?
Lathander works in mysterious ways.
All right, it's not like I'm putting any undead in this temple, not yet, yeah.
Sure, let's put Brittany.
Do you have that spell yet?
You'll get there.
All right, so Bryn and Iles, let's just put Bryn and Iles there so we don't forget that they exist.
Okay, all right.
So, Bryn and Iles are, you know, are very happy to be putting together the temple.
Harbin is very happy that it will now, you know, the Tresendar Manor, which has been in a state of disrepair, will be built.
You know, money and Jenerith turns to turns to you and turns to the three of you and says, See, this is what I mean about how money, when you take it as adventures and then put it back into the community, it becomes clean money.
See how it becomes, it becomes not really blood money, you're returning it to the people, right?
Almost as if it's been wandered, washed clean.
See, if you see how this works, so you could perhaps, you know, reach out to Vukradin in a little bit and make him see how this all works.
He's young, he's got a lot to learn.
Give him time.
I'm gonna be running this town.
Yes, I mean, you probably are destined for great things.
All right, all right, I'm gonna wander back into the table.
My cigarette is out, yeah, feeling thirsty.
All right, back in the tavern.
All right, so nighttime passes, unless there's anything else.
So, nothing happened while I was gone, right?
Nice things you're mind about all this nonsense about partnering with evil people.
We're just gonna found a temple here because, like, there's nothing in the temple, that's a good thing, right?
That's a good thing, yeah.
Where'd you get the money to do that?
Harbin says, Harbin interrupts my.
I just want you to know that this was a donation made by the community.
Oh, now he's helping about time.
Something good happened around here.
I think the community felt that this would be a good step forward and you know, bring maybe I won't have to replace you next week.
All right, about donating a free round of beer, Spider-Man.
I think that's an excellent idea.
I'll drink to that.
All right, Spider-Man shows up with the beers, uh, hands him over.
All right, morning, you wait, you go to sleep, you wake up in the morning, and um, just see if there's a bunch of quests that you're supposed to do.
I would like to talk to Sir Karen.
Okay, what do you want to ask him?
How are you doing in tracking down the rightful owners of all this treasure we've found that needs to be returned?
You said you were working on that for us.
Well, at a game, uh, Costanis hasn't figured that out yet.
So, Phil, Sir Karen, what are you doing?
He goes, Look, by the time, so look, let me see what is sick.
This, I need to check something out.
All right, did the butterskull on it?
He goes, Sir Kalin goes, Okay, so he goes, Well, I should be able to help you with that in a few days.
The message I sent up to Neverwinter should bring me should bring me back some information in a few days.
Sounds good.
All right, yeah, and um, in the meantime, you may want to go check out what's been going on at Mountain Toes.
Oh, yes, Mountain Toes, that does seem like the next place to go.
There was also Logger's Camp, yeah, Logger's Camp.
Harbin, Harbin hears the words love camp and gets very excited because that's uh something that hit for his brother that he wants with his brother.
Is that correct?
No, we just need to carry some supplies to the camp, yep, and in the direction of the carver.
No, you tell me, nice try.
Sister Kayla said she would give you some information in a few days, so you don't actually know where the carver is.
Ah, okay.
So, we need to either escort some guy to a gold mine or carry a bunch of supplies into the forest, right?
I vote for carrying supplies to the forest, okay?
Yeah, he's big and can carry things.
That's great.
Oh, yeah, well, you know, I guess Harbin just did me a solid by you know, donating this new chapel, so I guess I should try to help him out.
Hey, just keeps going.
Yeah, I like the man.
He handles free beer, he's a big believer.
Like, you know, why, why, why, all right, all right, okay, so he goes, uh, yeah, Harbin says that you need to go step bus provisions to collect the provisions to go to.
Wasn't I supposed to buy a rapier or something like that?
If you want, yeah, how much does that cost?
He says standard prices, so all right, I will look at it pretty cheap, yeah.
Whatever, whatever the standard price for that is.
How much provisions are we talking about, by the way, that we need to carry?
Do we need some sort of carriage or something?
Um, well, so you go to Barth.
Um, Barthon says, Where is it?
Wait, why didn't I click on this?
Like, did I not click on the right thing?
We're going to the loggers, right?
Is that what we said?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, so you have to go to Barth and.
Find out.
All right.
I'll go.
No, we can all go.
Yeah, there's probably gonna be a lot to carry.
Yeah, when you arrive to pick up the supplies, Barthen is there, and he tells you that his clerks have filled two crates with supplies as he hands you a sheet of parchment upon which is written an inventory of the crates constants: foodstuffs such as dried meats, blocks of cheese, and loaves of bread, as well as casks of ale and flasks of oil.
The two heavy crates are loaded onto a two-wheeled cart pulled by an ox.
Barthenon says, His name is Vincent, and I'll expect to see him and the cart returned.
Thanks.
Do we need the cart and the ox?
Well, it's two crates.
Yeah, yes.
I need at least one hand to fight if we meet somebody.
Yes, it down.
And hold on, those crates have bread and cheese and no wine.
That doesn't seem right.
He says, Wait, did you say you wanted some wine?
Absolutely.
Bread, you gotta have wine.
He goes, Well, turns out there is a hunting lodge on the way that you could stop at a hunting lodge that sells very fine wine.
All right, I turn to the group and say, What do you say, guys?
We go get ourselves some fine wine with this bread and cheese.
Some is down for wine.
All right, so I'm just going to show you where that is.
You should be able to see it now.
Do you see it?
Well, that was pretty far away.
It's a bit of a hike.
So, we need to task someone to a gold mine, right?
What?
The other quests.
We're going to do loggers camp first.
Oh, I see.
Oh, wow.
That is way out there.
The gold mine is kind of on the way, though.
You can do both.
You don't have to do, you don't have to do one.
You can do like them together.
It's not like you have to do one, come back, do the other.
Yeah, but I mean, do we take the cart and Vincent to the gold mine?
Doesn't seem super safe.
It could get a little, you know, lost damage along the way.
I mean, there, we have encountered many a bandit.
Sure, just uh, putting out there.
All right, so to the loggers, to the today, first day.
All right, so that's about a two days' journey.
50 miles, yeah.
Two days' journey.
Do we have provisions for two days?
That's not in the crate.
I mean, um, I'm assuming you have rations.
We, yeah, we don't usually track that stuff.
We don't track arrows and rations, all right, and only appropriate do we track very pretty big.
I eat a lot, so I believe that arrangement various bags of holding and such.
I see.
No, no, there's been a curious shortage of bags of holding.
Yeah, you don't want another bomb going off.
There are some curious, there have been some curious problems about finding bags of holding right, right?
What is it?
Export?
No, I can't remember.
All right, okay.
So, I presume we're going to the hunting lodge first wine.
Yes, we want wine.
You're very thirsty.
Absolutely.
Always.
Anyway, it's nice to break up the monotony, you know.
Okay, so, okay.
So, uh, before you go, uh, what says um then explains the falk hunting lodge is a sanctuary in the center of the heart of never winter wood.
It's uh, it's it's was maintained by Falcon the Hunter.
He offers his services as a guide to those nobles, most of them who wouldn't last long in the forest without his protection and survivor kill skills.
He abhors city lives, preferring a saristic existence and simple pleasures.
His lodge has all the creature comforts he requires.
He has two retainers, um, and he's he says this is a it is in addition to a hunting lodge and the main house, it includes a guest house for visitors, a stable house and smithy, an outhouse, and pens to hold the fast lion livestock.
Uh, you're free to stay, and he says, Uh, I would recommend you go there, and he offers a wonderful private room in the main lodge for a modesty.
Okay, maybe you could send him a note ahead of time, tell him we're coming and who we are and how awesome we are, and what we should have a say and all those things.
Roll your persuasion, a minimum 15, but if you'd like me to roll, yeah, because I want to see whether you get a natural 20, because I want to see what else whether you 15.
All right, so he says, Well, he goes, Well, I can't really go, but he scribbles down a note and hands it to you.
Okay, it is a bit of a journey, and I do have my store to manage.
Okay, did he like sign it, put his seal on it?
Yeah, it's clear that it's actually legit from him, okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's a legitimate networks, right?
He says, All right, so and so maybe you can entertain the patrons once we get there.
Uh, if you're good while we're in town, do we need to sell anything?
We have my old chain shirt to sell and then some blood money stuff.
I don't really sell that at the same time.
Chain shirt's organic, the rest is blood.
Yeah, yeah, go ahead, sell.
I assume the chain shirt.
And can I persuade for a better deal, please?
Minimum 15.
I assume the chain shirt that I brought with me from the Underdark is not blood, blood money shirt.
I probably wouldn't question that one.
Yeah, okay.
You assured me that it was yours.
It's definitely mine.
You see, negative prominence, definitely mine.
By now, it's Schrödinger's blood money.
I don't know.
So, you arrive at the Falcon Hunting Lodge.
I think we have some gems and stuff, too.
You could sell, Gary.
I don't know.
I mean, it looks like some of this is blood money, though.
Okay.
I don't know if we want to sell this spellbook just yet.
Until we find the rightful owners, what do we usually do with old Deloot?
We just leave it in the inventory.
We're hauling it around until we can return it.
Can they show you the blood money flag in the loot chart?
We're pretty sure that Brewbarry carries an entire barrel of wine with him everywhere he goes.
Just right on the right shoulder.
He doesn't need both shoulders.
Isn't there like some trope enemy trip for having a keg on your back?
Something like that.
Like a small keg.
Oh, there are definitely a bunch of app types of that.
Yeah.
You arrive at the Falcon Lodge.
Wow, that's it.
We've just made it.
No problem.
Yeah.
All the magic of Never With Wood and all that stuff didn't affect us.
Not this time.
Even the cart didn't slow us down.
We weren't as navigators.
We weren't.
The ancient ruins weren't obscured to us.
No, because stay away from the, you know, because they give you nasty stuff.
No, no, I mean, sometimes, sometimes you arrive there.
It's kind of a disappointment almost.
Like there was like nothing happened.
It was like, it was just a boring, you know, two-day trip.
It wasn't boring.
It's a nice nature hike.
We sang songs.
We were out in nature.
Yeah, I would say it was drinking a lot.
We drank some.
We didn't steal anything.
Nope.
Not a single thing.
All right.
A thin fog surrounds a fortified compound standing in a clearing on the east side of the narrow river.
A 10-foot-high log palisade surrounds the compound, whose main building is a two-story stone wood affair with a high-pitched roof, gables, window shutters, and a stone chimney.
Attached to the main building is a blocky tower of gray stone.
Its high roof lined with other structures include a two-story stable house and a gift whose flat roof is enclosed by iron railings.
A stone bridge spans the river, ending before an oaken door set into the gate outer wall.
Mounted next to the door is a bell with a short rope hanging from its clappers.
Ring the bell?
I think you ring the bell.
We're not going to break it, are we?
No, I hope not.
I wonder why they have such a fence.
You said it's the feet pale.
I didn't show the map yet.
Yeah, we're still on the world map.
There.
Recticulating splines.
Looks like a battle map.
No, I know.
I'm going to get rid of the since there's no supposed to be somewhat of a not violent place.
Let me just do something here.
Spoiler.
Ringing the bell.
That's the plan.
I'm asked.
I mean, that's my plan, unless you got a better idea.
We could just.
Is there anything amiss?
I mean, if there's nothing amiss, then.
No, there is nothing.
He didn't ask us to roll perception.
It must be safe.
Do you open?
Do you walk up and ring the doorbell?
Night.
Turns out there is literally nothing bad going on.
Ring the damn bell.
All right.
Go for it.
Go for it, Soma.
All right.
Soma rings the bell.
Hello.
Well, that's what the problem is.
All right.
You ring the bell.
The bell was rung.
And what happens?
I need to get what's his name.
All right.
Okay.
You two need to get a commoner.
Or it's worth this.
Is all fog of war inside?
Yeah, I know.
I know.
We're going to fix that.
Hold on.
All right.
Corwin.
This guy looks you over, says, Who are you?
I'm Soma.
Note, hand him the note.
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Oh, he looks at it and goes, You're from Barthon sent you.
Well, come in, come in.
I'm sure the Falcon Hunter will want to chat with you.
Right.
He's like, so what?
Stand in the corner.
It's well guarded.
You're standing in the corner?
Yeah.
All right.
What news do you have from the logging cap?
You know, I don't do the nose.
I don't do the news.
Let me get the falcon hunter.
He can talk to you.
Who are you?
What's your name?
My name is.
Although my friends call me chef.
You're not my friends yet, so you can call me Corwin.
All right.
Do you do a lot of cooking?
Well, you know, I'm the cook the meals here.
Yeah, that would be what I do.
I also do.
So you're the chef.
Yeah, you could say that.
Okay.
Do you also make wine?
Can you tell me about the wine?
Oh, let me get the falcon hunter.
He's the one you really want to be talking about.
He really doesn't want to talk to us.
No, not Falcon Hunter.
Falcon the Hunter.
Yeah, Falcon the Hunter.
He's the guy you want to talk to, not me.
Fucking druid.
I love his side prints.
Another druid.
Those are full-on mutton chops, dude.
All right.
Can you guys see him?
Yeah.
Yes, we see him.
He goes, my goodness.
My goodness.
Guests.
Wonderful.
It's been a while since I've seen any guests.
All right.
I guess I should move in and charm him.
Work your magic face.
You are.
The letter.
Present the letter.
My goodness, my good friend.
Barthen invited you here.
That is an excellent, excellent, excellent activity for me to hear.
Yeah, we're on our way to the loggers' camp.
You're on your way to the logger's camp.
I mean, I assume he sees the cart we have in tow, right?
Yeah, he goes, well, you know, I, first of all, I think you should spend the night here.
We'll have a wonderful meal.
I, and if, if we have a band who will perform for you, oh, that would be spick, sure, happy to.
He looks at uh Valphine.
He goes, I don't mean to be rude.
Oh, good.
I'm glad you're not rude.
No, I, I, you are a drow, yes.
Oh, yes.
So much racism.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It happens to be that I have another staying with me, and I would think she would be delighted to have dinner with you.
Can we handle two drows?
Okay.
I'm kind of curious.
Like, is that okay?
You want to have dinner with her?
What is her name?
No, I don't recall it off the top of my head.
He's trying to set you up.
Enough of the chit-chat.
Tell us about the wine.
Priorities.
I love a good barbarian.
And you are.
Your name is.
I'm the wine drinker.
Tell me about the wine.
I go, well, Brewbarry.
He's Brewbarry.
Good friend.
I keep some of the best wine in the area in my cellar.
Good.
I'm thirsty.
He goes, excellent.
I must warn you, it's not the cheapest wine.
Nothing.
We are friends of Bartholomew and whatever his name is.
Yes, yes, you know, such a good friend.
He goes, well, well, you know, I could be if Falcon Falcon goes, I can't give you an infinite supply, but certainly I could give you a few bottles.
And if the bard here was to play some dunes tonight to keep us entertained, I'm certain I could bring out some more wine to keep us all pleasantly happy.
I don't think you can stop happy to play for beer.
I sort of tower over him and I'm like, make that barrel and you got a chance.
He kind of looks at you and he sort of laughs heartily and he says, well, well, well, well, I think we will be good friends here.
I think we will be good friends here.
Yes.
All right.
So he brings you to the dinner.
So he says, well, let's.
And so, you know, a few hours later, he goes, and while you're here, you might as well just sit down, relax, check out, and we will have dinner in the dining room.
That's a great place to eat.
Look around while we're here.
Well, I don't really relax, though.
I turn to him and I say, why such a big fence around this tavern?
Oh, yes, good question.
He says, that is an excellent question.
You know, ever since the dragon showed up, the orc have left their mountain homes and have now descended into the valley.
I've seen more orcs of wood in the woods of late.
Ugly, ugly brutes.
From out here, just, you know, because it's kind of a small space and they would probably perform out.
No, no, no, no.
No, he goes, he wants you to perform in the dining room.
It's going to be really loud.
The dining room is very large.
It's not that big.
Is this not the dining room?
Yeah, that's a dining room.
That's like a 40 by 80 foot area.
All right.
Really?
So, where do they stay?
I'll hear you.
To his cellar.
The wine cellar.
No, they don't.
Well, so this is the dining room.
And upstairs is his bedroom, is his deluxe guest bed, his deluxe guest bedroom, his personal bedroom.
That's what's upstairs.
Staying in the deluxe guest bedroom?
He goes, he goes, well, if the music is good, why not?
16, yeah, definitely.
Do we need to do the performance check?
That was persuasion.
Sure, we can do a performance check.
Good night.
Very good.
What if the music we're playing this time?
A pop death metal?
Isn't that what we do?
Okay.
Our usual.
The usual.
So do I need to do my singing check here?
Yes, you need to do your singing.
All right.
So we noticed the...
You're the law.
We're wanting you.
You know, it was good.
All right, Yoko.
Take a back seat.
Now take it, Goko.
So, so while all this good entertainment takes place, I ask if there are people standing watch around the fence as well.
The fence is good, but if there's who's standing watch, he goes, well, you know, I don't really need.
They know not to come here.
And I've got he pauses and I'm they know not to trouble me, but if they trouble me, they'll be dead.
Okay.
This is what works.
Yes.
He's a very arrogant guy.
Kind of has that look of like, you know, they won't mess with me.
This is getting so raised by the end of the campaign, isn't it?
What?
This is going to be so burned down by the end of the campaign.
He then explains, although he pauses as so, so let's see.
So this is the dining room.
Let's see what else.
Brave of you to think that it's going to last that long, Wade.
I said by the end of the camp.
The carver doesn't bother him here?
You didn't ask about that.
Philosopher doesn't bother you here.
He is the carver.
Because he's been hiring orcs.
He goes, the carver?
Who's the carver?
He's a bandit leader.
Been terrorizing.
People around these parts.
He goes, oh, yes, I've heard rumors about this man.
We have our friend with us.
What's his name?
Corbin.
Yeah.
Another.
Oh, there's Corbin.
He's with Corwin.
Yes.
That's lame.
Well, you know, I didn't like.
You know, he says, oh, bandits.
Well, that would explain some things.
Explain what?
Like what?
All the banditry?
Well, no, I mean, I thought it was only the orcs, but I have noticed that the orcs have done, there's been, there has been a few more organized than usual.
Yes, that would be exactly what I was about to say.
They seem a little bit more organized.
Yeah, they lay traps and other weird things now.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And that may explain why the orcs appear to be in league with some evil half-orcs.
Evil half-works.
Evil half-orcs.
Yes, there's some evil half-works that dwell southwest of here.
Are they a problem for you?
Well, I mean, not really, but they do dwell in a ruined stone manse overgrown with vines roughly 10 miles from here.
Are they the legal owners of that?
No.
Do you know who is?
Well, it was abandoned.
It was abandoned.
Yes.
So then they are the remote.
Squatters, right?
It's not how that works.
You still don't understand the overburden.
He's like, look, he goes, he's saying, yes, they are.
You know, I don't think they're much of a broad.
They don't bother me.
They don't bother me too much.
And if they were to do anything, I could handle them.
But, you know, they do their.
Yeah, you seem quite powerful.
Well, you know, I've been here for many years.
Do you ever go out?
And do you ever do anything?
Oh, you seem like the type.
He goes, those days are long past me.
Why?
Well, because I like having my...
I like doing what I'm doing now.
Okay.
I retired from a retired from a benchmark.
He pauses.
He goes, he goes, he pauses.
You know, I learned something about adventuring.
There's not many old adventurers.
Dead.
There's young adventurers.
A lot of young adventurers.
There's young adventurers and there's retired old adventurers.
There's no old adventurers who are still in.
Excuse me.
What do you make of me?
He pauses.
He goes, he looks at you and goes, oh, he's kind of like realized that he's put his foot in his knit and he's a bit, you know, like, he's like, I didn't mean it, blah, blah, blah.
I'm sure Valphine is at least 70 or 80, but she hasn't considered herself old since.
Yes.
So he's like, so I, you know, in my experience, it's best to take the point of view that adventurers should retire once they've made a pile of money.
Well, it's not about how long you live your life, it's how you live your life.
I completely agree.
And I have chosen to live my life as a owner of a in the wilderness where I get to go hunting and periodically have guests come over whom I help hunt.
And I make money and I take care of my animals and I have fine wine and drink, eat fine meals.
What did you say?
Must have done a lot of noble quests to earn such money.
Does anybody warn him before he says the next sentence?
He's not in our party.
He can stick his foot in his mouth all he wants.
What does he say?
What's the real thing?
Is there something that I'm supposed to be catching with insight here?
Yeah, you're about to catch with insight.
He may not know about Vukradin.
Yeah, you definitely are about, you definitely pick up with insight that he may suddenly start talking about treasures he plundered, monsters he killed.
Wait, so I pick up that he's going to talk about that.
Yes.
And that's normal to me, right?
And you don't quite understand what's going on with Vukradin, so I don't.
I don't think you would interrupt.
You see the train coming and you're like, I'm going to stand right in the middle of the tracks.
Yeah, I want to watch it come close.
Yeah, that's the right way.
You just want to make sure.
The light, it's so bright.
I mean, trites for me.
In his case, that would literally be what she would do.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So the Falcon says, yes, I did, in fact, made quite a bit of money from why there was this dragon that my group killed, and it had a large horde that we split four ways.
And part of that horde is how I built this.
Sounds right.
Yeah, he's like, it was that horde that allowed me.
I'm going to go have that diamond.
We're done.
We're not playing here.
I will not perform in this venue.
He goes, but he goes, that was many years ago.
Now I only do...
He let's see.
Okay, he really doesn't pick up on it.
He goes, I don't know what I said, but I want you to know that ever since then, I only take guests that pay for their fees.
And, you know, this is all owned.
It wasn't enough that you had to steal from all those people killed by the dragon.
You continue to take more money.
Wait, aren't we guests here?
Is this how to take it?
By the way, there's supposed to be some drought here, too, right?
Yes.
Cigarette.
You're going to grab a cigarette.
All right.
I got him.
So Vukradin grabbed a guest.
The Falcon Hunter looks at the rest of you with this kind of look of like, so do the rest of you think I'm thieves?
I'm a thief.
He has some strange ways.
Hmm.
Well, if the rest of you don't think I'm a thief, I suppose I could forgive your friend here, but he will not be having any free wine.
Okay.
Your wine, your choice.
And then he pauses and he says, no, no, he pauses.
I've heard this rumor that's been going around about this new movement against adventures using plunder.
It's all part, it's all part of some sort of attempt to disrupt the ruling elite and to force the imposition of law and order and move away from the barbaric violence of adventuring.
It's like a new economic system.
Yeah, so he goes, I've heard these rumors.
It's all nonsense, if you ask me.
He goes, the purpose of adventures is to adventure, to take the gold, and to plow it back into the communities.
That's one way.
The adventure can be the reward of its own, you know.
Oh, he goes, I couldn't.
I like that.
He goes, so that is extremely wise.
And obviously, a total of your wisdom will most definitively enjoy dinner tonight.
All right.
So dinner arrives.
Let's see.
I should go put my character where I really am.
Definitely not.
I need to exit a roll tones.
I'm sulking over here eating rations.
You're not going to be dancing.
You're not going to be singing.
Is that what I hear?
No.
He's not going to play.
He's not going to play for a blood money or a thief, whatever.
But he's performed already, right?
So we sort of.
I'm done.
The set's over.
Yeah, he played.
It was a great set, too.
It was.
Wasted.
Hold on, guys.
Well, it got the rest of us a bunch of free liquor.
See what I do for my friends?
Yeah.
We're friends now.
Well done.
Saved your life a few times.
Yeah.
I think you actually killed them, too.
I have no remarks.
I thought I did some damage, didn't I?
Yeah.
I think you accidentally killed Soma, if I recall correctly.
I thought it was the other one.
I thought I accidentally earth primered on the party.
Or Ice Knife or something like that.
Oh, no, yeah, yeah, it was.
It was the ice knife.
Yeah.
I'm still figuring out how to be a druid.
All right.
Yeah.
This druid thing is new to me.
It's just how it goes.
I can turn into bear.
I'm good at that.
Yeah, you're a good bear.
That was before I could transform.
Correct.
So I need a name.
All right.
So you arrive at the Falcon Lodge.
You arrive for dinner.
Oh, okay.
Dinner.
We've been at the Falcon Lodge.
Yeah, sorry.
I meant the dinner part.
And there is, in fact, a drow.
And she sits, she sits down at a dinner with the rest of you.
Do I recognize her?
No.
Okay.
Sir, I need to get a drow.
Well, I guess I would strike up a conversation.
Have you come up here to enjoy the pain of you see?
All right, look at this drow here.
All right.
Need to give her a name.
I have the name.
Just give me one second.
Her name is Sridar.
No, that's not the one.
Just put the name down.
All right.
She goes, oh, another fellow resident of the Underdark.
I noticed you're here.
Yes, but I've moved up here, where it is much, much more delightfully painful.
He pauses and looks at.
She pauses and looks and goes, Are you a cleric of Lothander?
Why, yes.
You do understand the pain that light causes to drow.
Yes?
Yes.
Oh, does she ever masochist?
But she whispers, you're really a cleric of Loth, right?
No, no.
No?
No.
This is not some illiberate ruse.
Not this time.
Okay.
All right.
So she's.
What brings you up here?
Well, I've become quite a collector of sorts.
And what do you collect?
I've heard rumors of disruptions in the area.
Oh, yes.
We know about this.
And I was wondering, and I've been looking for any kind of little curio you might have found, something that's not quite right.
I've become very interested in those things.
Do we have something like that?
Yeah, didn't we pick something up?
You did pick something up.
Well, we sold all that stuff.
It wasn't.
No, the Black Pearl was from the Lighthouse.
I think we sold it all.
Talisman at Moscow.
Talisman.
Oh, plot items.
I always inscribed.
Talisman?
Talisman of Moscow, yeah.
Of Moscow.
Yes.
So that would be, that would be definitely something that was very weird.
Peculiar.
Yes.
Do we think it's important to us?
It says plot item, but do we care about it?
He goes, I'm willing to pay.
She goes, she goes, I'm willing to pay good money for any such device or gadget you find.
I think I've become quite the word she's looking for.
Collector.
And what can you do with such a thing?
Does one need a reason to collect curious things?
I got.
I'm the naive one.
We'd like to know before we sell.
How about that?
Why is what is going on with these planar incursions?
It seems to have got all the druids up here pretty feisty.
About half of them.
She goes, Look, I really can't.
I don't know.
Ever since that, the incident involving the blink in the underdark when the face went blink and the demons came in, I've become quite intrigued.
That's what happened in the past.
And she goes, after the blink, after the blink, I've become very interested in learning more about planar events and planar transformations.
And I thought it would be a wonderful thing for me to look at.
Natasha's every time she walks in, announces DPK.
17 that I gain from some insights.
She's genuinely interested in those things.
She's like, it's like a genuine, real interest.
Oh, wait.
We need to know whether you're an interventionist.
I am not anymore.
Or sorry.
No, no, I'm not a naturalist anymore.
I thought I was a naturalist until I saw what batshit insanity the nurturalists were.
And I think now I'd be qualified as an interventionist.
But the naturalists are on the batshit crazy side.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not batshit crazy.
I want there to be a world tomorrow.
Do you aim to intervene in the planar effects?
I would like to stop for incursions, yes.
Yeah, so but Sridar says she looks at what is this?
There's a schism going on in the Emerald Enclave, I guess.
I don't know.
I'm not really part of them.
I'm a late-stage, late-in-life druid, you know?
The Falcon the Hunter goes, Yes, Adabra and her ilk are convinced that everything evil comes from anyone intervening and trying to protect the world, and so we should just let it all burn to the ground.
Yes, they're off their rockers.
Yes, they're off the rockers.
Sridar goes, Oh, Falcon, yes, we were talking about that just the other day.
I thank you for reminding me.
I'd forgotten about that.
No, of course not.
I have nothing to do with that.
I'm just a collector.
I don't, I am not a member of the Emerald Enclave.
I'm just a collector, a person who finds things interesting, that kind of thing.
So, do we want to be interventionists in the planar things?
Like, is that Prom is in favor of that?
I don't think anybody in the party was particularly comfortable with the shit coming into the audience.
Yeah, just let it all go to hell.
It seems like a problem.
Yes, we should stop it.
Yes, she goes, but says, I think you should stop it, but I am just collecting items.
Look, do you have anything?
Any information, any stories you might tell me?
I'm willing to pay for either.
I tell you a story.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, you're actually the one that watched the little dude collecting shit at the end, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, overall perception to see how well I remember the circumstances of that.
And then, I mean, 23.
All right, so yes.
I remember quite a bit of detail.
Right.
She, uh, Sridar.
This is very interesting.
I've never heard of such creatures and such events.
And is this place still there?
Yes.
Didn't it all swallow up?
No, no.
Well, you guys left.
Oh, yeah.
We left.
Yeah.
You left.
I stopped the patrol thing, right?
No, you were.
She goes, well, well, well, this is very, very important.
But for this kind of information, if you ever find it, I would gladly give you gold.
Would 20 gold be enough?
And wine?
You should go get me from outside to persuade her.
Okay.
Falcon's going to demand an apology.
Refreshments is part of the real world as well.
So you show up here, right?
And he demands an apology.
What does he want me to apologize for?
Well, for calling him all common thief.
I'm sorry.
You're a good host.
Yes, and you and you roll a 15%.
I know.
I got to roll deception.
14.
But don't you have a silver tongue on deception?
With the four.
Yeah, minimum 10, and then I get the plus four.
Yes, that's how it works.
The falcon is very good.
You get minimum 14 deception, minimum 15 persuasion.
He buys it.
Silver tongue.
Now I got to persuade the drought to give us more money.
I'd really rather him tell us more about the planar incursions.
Yeah, that too.
I want to know.
Don't forget about the wine.
We love Brewbarry.
Want me to ask who asked for wine?
Refreshments.
Anything.
Corwin shows up with more wine.
Okay.
Excellent.
So just Corwin shows up with more wine.
All right.
Okay.
So the Falcon Hunter.
So Sridar.
So what did you ask?
I'm sorry.
So Sridar looks at you and says, well, I thought 20 gold pieces was a ridiculous amount of money.
30 gold pieces.
That's a 50% increase.
Not too bad.
And she goes, but if you have any artifacts, information is valuable, but the artifacts would be extremely valuable.
Well, show her the talisman.
I don't want to agree to sell it yet.
I want to know if there's anything valuable about it.
Obviously, you shouldn't pay for it.
It's got to have some more letters.
Study it.
No, she goes, Oh, yes, yes, yes.
This is definitely there's definitely a planar connection with this thing.
Absolutely.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
She goes, I'll buy it from you.
Well, tell us more about it first.
I don't know if we're selling, but we'd be happy to let you study it for a fee.
Guys, dude, it's fair trade gold.
We rarely get an opportunity to get real money.
Let's do it.
It's just sitting around in our backpack.
I forgot we even had it.
I'm more worried what she's going to do with it.
You know, maybe she's going to go make her own little interest.
She's just a drow.
I mean, drow or I'll find.
Oh, yes.
Nothing's more trustworthy than a drow.
Thank you.
Wait, are you saying that you have issues with?
I would say Vukradin Valphine seems at least neutral.
So he's not inclined to think that this drow is inherently evil.
I mean, we've heard the stories.
No, I think Vukradin hasn't heard this.
Vukradin's young and dumb, yes.
Vukradin heard.
He's pro sell it and get the money because it's fair trade gold.
All right.
So she takes it and says, Well, she pauses and says, I don't know very much about this, but there's been many of these items that have been.
Well, the stories are that there have been all sorts of trinkets that are imbued with planar energies that have appeared in the area.
Why?
If I knew why, I would tell you.
The information I have.
So what are you doing?
You're up here exploring and researching.
She goes, ever since the blink and the demons appeared.
The nature of their existence has fascinated me.
In fact, that is why the Falcon and I chatted about the intervention.
And the naturalists, the naturalists were of the opinion, if it was up to the naturalists, the demon lords underground would have torn the entire planet apart, whereas the interventionists would have saved them.
And I am absolutely an interventionist, especially after what happened in Menzoberranzan.
Oh, did you live there too?
Well, no, but I heard about it.
Oh, okay.
You don't know why it's happening, but what's your theory?
It could be anything.
It could be magic users.
It could be planar entities.
It could be fools meddling with things they don't understand.
It could be all sorts of things.
What exactly it is, I don't know.
That's actually a very good question.
Maybe you'd like to help us figure this out.
Well, she goes, I would be delighted to help you figure this out.
If you ever find any more information, just come to me.
And I'd be more than delighted to see whether I could piece a few clues together.
Do you have any leads for us?
I've never really thought about it.
She goes, I never really thought of it as actually being intentional, but you know, now that you ask it, there might be something going on here.
I just thought this was a natural phenomenon.
She goes, after all, as Athina knows, in the Underdark, we have the Faerzress, which is an extra reward.
And from the oak, of course, I lived in the Under for years.
And when I came up here, I heard about these artifacts, and I thought this was just another example of how the world works.
Yes.
That makes sense to me.
I mean, the world is a hostile and dangerous place that's trying to kill you.
Yeah.
Yes, exactly.
I mean, think about it.
You people walk out in the sun all day.
Yeah.
Like a dangerous, hostile environment.
Yeah, it burns.
It's hot.
It makes you sweat.
Well, I'm not the brightest barbarian, but all those events happening within the same area, how likely is it that it's a coincidence?
How much were we going to get for the she hasn't quoted yet?
I find Vukradin very greedy for honest bob.
Does not see a lot of it.
He says, wow, she says, about a hundred gold pieces.
Would that be and wine?
She turns to the falcon and give this man three bottles of wine.
He just paid the gold pieces to get the wine for Brewbarry.
That was nice of her.
Yeah, and then on a side note, because the 30 went to, she doesn't have any more money, dude.
Oh, okay.
120.
I don't know what she's going to do with it.
That's a lot of money for something that she's just collecting.
The thing about the rich is money doesn't have the same sort of, you know, they start to lose joy from everyday activities.
They need to look for new ways to get out of life and spending their money is how they do it.
And they'll buy all sorts of things.
It's just how it goes.
I thought you were broke, so how would you know?
Persuasion on it.
Let her buy it.
That's fine.
Just for the record, Stefan, we said that he can roll persuasion, but characters, players.
Oh, I know.
It doesn't actually have an effect.
No, I'll eat it, though.
It's fine.
No, no, no.
And so players can choose to eat it.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Yes.
Fair enough.
So, yeah, just to be clear.
Yes, he can roll and you can say yes.
I just want to point out it's a very persuasive speech that I guess.
Who responds to it?
Is up to her.
All right.
I'm fine.
So after dinner, The Falcon, the Hunt.
Okay.
I'm going to record it.
Yep.
You darn well.
That's a lot of gold for me.
You already did.
Okay.
Is this person a.
Are you an adventurer?
No, I'm not.
No adventure.
I'm just a traveler, a refugee.
How do you stay safe coming so far from home?
Do you have a bodyguard?
Well, the Falcon Hunter.
No, no, I'm not talking to Falcon.
I'm talking to the driver.
She's explaining.
Falcon the Hunter.
She paid for him to bring her here.
Oh.
Oh, you're with him.
Yes.
She's.
Okay.
Why that is.
What?
Why?
No, no, not.
Oh, I've got nothing.
I got nothing to say.
Not in that way.
I'm good.
She's very confused, right?
Why is she?
She put guests in his home.
Yes, yes.
All right.
Okay.
After a wonderful dinner.
Did she hear my death chat earlier?
And it bombed.
Yes.
Okay.
That's why she asked, are you really a cleric of Lolth?
It didn't sound like Llira music.
It sounded more like Lolth clerical chants.
A lot of clicking sounds.
So there's a lot of clicking, a Lolthian.
There's a lot of eight-note beats.
Well done.
Okay.
All right.
So he does say, but you know, he says, well, there is a bit of a there's a bit of a challenge I have.
He goes, so he does give you an additional quest you can choose to explore.
The half-works?
The mants, yes.
Say again?
The Woodland Mants.
Just put that.
Is that the half-works?
Yes.
Okay.
Woodland Mants.
That's mants.
Let me.
Okay.
What does he want us to do exactly?
Investigate the preemptive strike.
Well, those half-orgs have stolen a lot of things.
Well, hold on.
Let me answer.
So he goes, he's like, right now that they don't seem to be causing any problems.
So he goes, I don't really have anything to say.
But, you know, if you ever decide to go.
Actually, hold on.
Hold on.
All right.
So he looks at you and says, he says, well, I could have a quest for you, but I think you need to get a little bit more experience before you're ready to handle it.
So there's been the half-war?
Yes.
All right.
Before we break, I'd like to, since you'll have to figure this one out, while everyone is sleeping, I would like to search for the dragon horde so that I can get information on it.
Okay.
You're not going to steal it from.
I think I won't steal it.
I think what I want to do is get information and go get the rightful owner of that stuff to come here to try to make our hunter friend understand what he has done in keeping the stuff from whose it is rightfully.
It was the dragon that stole it all originally.
But yeah.
Well, yeah.
But our friend kept the horde instead of returning it.
Yeah.
So you said, who does the horde belong to, right?
Does it belong to the dragons are very possessive about their horde.
Well, the dragon is dead.
Who does Gumberto work for?
Yeah, now the horde or a quarter of the horde belongs to our friend the hunter.
But let's see if we can figure out who the original owner was.
That'll be hard.
Yeah.
We don't actually have any sort of provenance magic, right?
I think I have like identify or stuff like that.
Does that actually reveal that kind of thing?
What did we need?
We needed legend lore.
Is that what we determined?
Yeah.
I believe I had locate object, but I don't think that helped.
I mean, it would help you find like the other half of a Gaffef necklace or something.
Okay.
All right.
So he does say when you, when you, he got, he does say, all right.
So he does actually.
Talk to them.
No, no, no.
I'm just going to say he does offer, he says, if you do ever, by the way, deal with the half-orcs and the Woodland Mants, there's a boot, there's a pair of boots of elven kind for you.
Okay.
You're going to give you have boots of elven kind which you're going to give to us.
Yes.
But what size do I have?
The good news is these boots can fit at any fits all.
They adjust their size.
He does make a point, though.
He says he looks at he look he goes.
Don't worry.
I purchased those boots.
I'm going to hold my coffee with proceeds.
Stolen gold.
With the proceeds of this establishment.
Establishment built on stolen gold.
Yes.
Soma is finally starting to understand.
Oh, that's why Soma doesn't say that.
He's trying really hard to tell you that this is this.
I'm just sitting there.
I'm not going to say anything.
And you're, you're, you're, you're, he's generous of you to share your home with us.
And he goes.
And your wine.
All right.
Okay.
So Tuesday.
Are folks free next Friday?
Yeah, we'll be back in Texas.
No, Thursday would be better.
Thursday?
Can I do that?
Thursday will be, you know, like again, it'll be in York.
It'll be midnight.
Sliding out Friday morning, York next week, too.
I will be back Friday evening, California time.
Let's do Friday.
David couldn't do that.
I think I'm probably past then.
All right.
The reason I'm saying that is going without me on Thursday or Tuesday.
We could go without you on Thursday.
Or Tuesday.
I can't do Tuesday.
So let's do Thursday.
And if Gary, you decide to join us, you decide to join us.
Okay, it'll be mid.
And I will be getting up first later for it'll be midnight for me too, if that makes you feel better.
And I'll also have a lot of four hours, less or more, you know.
Yeah, we're doing the same thing, Gary.
You can sleep on the plane.
Okay, well, it's up to you.
So here's the deal: we'll try.
We're saying for Thursday, if it works out, it works out.
Yeah.
If it works out, it works out.
Just so you know, the week after, the reason I said we should try to meet next week is because the week after, I'm going to be in India, and then the week after that, I'm going to be in Belgium.
The India might be a little bit tricky because there's like all-day off sites, but in Belgium, I'll find out.
Where are you in India?
Bangalore.
Oh, me too.
You're going to be in Bangalore next week?
No, the same week you're going to be there.
Dude, we should like meet up and like stare at each other.
Although I hear it really depends where you are in Bangalore because it's like three hours from one side of the city to the other.
No, no, one side of the city, it's three blocks.
Going three blocks takes three.
All right.
Bye, guys.
Thank you.